<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Powersale</string>

    <!--   About Powersale -->
    <string name="about_text">Powersale brings an international audience of millions to the heart of the bidding action in Art, antiques, Jewelry and Collectibles auctions across the globe. With fascinating objects up for bid in more than 50 countries -instantly translated to your language and currency Powersale is a worldwide marketplace with treasures. waiting to be discovered, whether you are an avid collector or first-time visitor. By hosting thousands of auctions in real time via the Internet, the site allows unprecedented access to remote sales, and savvy bidders can often land desired items at very desirable prices. Leave an absentee bid, or fully engage in the live-auction action-it is up to you. All bidding takes place via a secure bidder network, which keeps your maximum bids for upcoming sales private until the item is opened on the day of the sale.Powersale revolutionized the industry from the start. In 2002, the NYC-based company formed a marketing partnership with eBay to introduce eBay Live Auctions. This alliance of Powersale and eBay enabled auction houses worldwide to go online with their live sales-a development that changed the auction business forever. In 2009, the debut of Powersale iPhone and Android apps, with live-bidding capabilities, opened up a new mobile pipeline to bid anytime, from anywhere, with complete anonymity. Since then, Powersale has been the first to engage bidders with live streaming video, easy online payments, personalized search alerts, and more. Now in its second decade, Powersale is the Web is leading auction-related site, with millions of qualified bidders. Powersale also provides a constant stream of industry intelligence to auctioneers, collectors, museums, appraisers, consignors and more via: The easy-to-use Auction Results Database, a vast database with more than 21 million results that offers keyword-search access to verified auction outcomes, recent to historical. The updated archive is the #1 free online resource for the trade, appraisers, collectors, designers, art institutions, estate officers, journalists, students and others on the research trail; Auction Central News, the global destination for the latest auction headlines, mixing timely industry news with feature articles by experts on all things design; The Powersale Consignment Hub or, an easy way for interested consignors to share their property for review and evaluation with thousands of auction houses in one spot. There are many ways to get started as a collector. You can browse curated auctions, find auctions near you, set up keyword search alerts, search, bid and win. If you are interested in selling online, share your consignment. Powersale award-winning customer support services are always available if you have questions. </string>

    <!--   for the spinner, dropdown menu-->
    <string-array name="spinn">
        <item>Poor UI</item>
        <item>Poor Service</item>
        <item>Lacking Performance</item>
        <item>Account Problems</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- for recycler view -->
    <string-array name="carlist_name">
        <item>Renault Kwid</item>
        <item>Suzuki Swift</item>
        <item>Suzuki Baleno</item>
        <item>Tata Tiago</item>
        <item>Toyota Innova</item>
        <item>Suzuki XL6</item>
        <item>Audi Q7</item>
        <item>Ferrari 296 GTB</item>
        <item>Hyundai Creta</item>
        <item>Toyota Hyryder</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="carlist_mileage">
        <item>12 kmpl</item>
        <item>13 kmpl</item>
        <item>16 kmpl</item>
        <item>13 kmpl</item>
        <item>7 kmpl</item>
        <item>11 kmpl</item>
        <item>5 kmpl</item>
        <item>4 kmpl</item>
        <item>10 kmpl</item>
        <item>12 kmpl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="carlist_price">
        <item>5.60 Lakh</item>
        <item>7.20 Lakh</item>
        <item>8.50 Lakh</item>
        <item>6.70 Lakh</item>
        <item>23.20 Lakh</item>
        <item>14.30 Lakh</item>
        <item>95.60 Lakh</item>
        <item>3.02 Cr</item>
        <item>11.10 Lakh</item>
        <item>17.60 Lakh</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>